http://www.hilcoglobal.com/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy
Share
Privacy Policy
Hilco is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Hilco Online Privacy Statement below. This Privacy Statement applies to data collected by Hilco through its Websites.
Collection of Your Personal Information
In order to access some Hilco information, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password, which we refer to as your credentials. By signing in on one Hilco site, you may be automatically signed into other Hilco sites. As part of creating your credentials, you may also be requested to provide questions and secret answers, which we use to help verify your identity and assist in resetting your password, as well as an alternate email address.
At some Hilco sites, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, work address or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code. We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with Hilco sites. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.
When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mail from Hilco, we may use web beacons, customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.
In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with Hilco, information collected through one Hilco site may be combined with information obtained through other Hilco sites. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies. Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any. Change/correct any data we have about you. Have us delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Use of Your Contact Information
Hilco collects and uses your contact information to carry out the transactions you have requested and to communicate with you through various media. We may send certain communications such as letters, event reminders and information on Hilco business transactions and personnel, and/or transaction-related data. Personal information collected on Hilco sites may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Hilco, its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a Hilco site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Hilco abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Sharing of Your Contact Information
Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Hilco and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent. Some Hilco services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you use such services, both Hilco and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.
Communication Preferences
You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Hilco sites and services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.
Security of Your Contact Information
Hilco is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. If a password is used to help protect your contact information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.
Use of Cookies
Hilco Web sites may use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Hilco Web sites may use cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Hilco sites and services that depend on cookies.
Controlling "Spam" or Unsolicited E-mail
Hilco is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail, or "spam." Hilco will not sell, lease or rent its e-mail subscriber lists to third parties.
Enforcement of This Privacy Statement
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our Web Sites and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement or in how Hilco will use your contact information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Hilco is protecting your information.
Contacting Us
Hilco welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us:
Hilco Privacy, The Hilco Organization,
5 Revere Drive, Suite 206,
Northbrook, IL 60062.
847-509-1100.
Contact Us
Learn how we can help you understand & maximize the value
of your assets.
Contact Us
